Guide to the Reuben A. Holden, Secretary of Yale University, Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- University Secretary: Subject File, 1901-1972; Series III
  - Commencement
    - 1963
      - Luncheon (Box 200, Folder 367)
      - Procedure (Box 201, Folder 368-369)
      - Programs (Box 201, Folder 371)
      - Special letters, Masters, Deans (Box 201, Folder 372)
      - Student Marshalls (Box 201, Folder 373)
    - 1964
      - Baccalaureate (Box 201, Folder 374)
      - Correspondence (Box 201, Folder 375)
      - Class Day (Box 201, Folder 376)
      - Degree forms (Box 201, Folder 377)
      - Dorr, Harry B. (Box 201, Folder 378)
      - Letters to Deans, officers, Masters (Box 201, Folder 379)
      - Luncheon (Box 202, Folder 380)
      - Pictures (Box 202, Folder 381)
      - Programs (Box 202, Folder 382)
      - Requisitions (Box 202, Folder 383)
      - Service Bureau and orders (Box 202, Folder 384)
      - Student Marshalls (Box 202, Folder 385)
    - 1965
      - Correspondence, memoranda (Box 202, Folder 386-387)
      - Class Day (Box 202, Folder 388)
      - Diploma orders (Box 202, Folder 389)
      - Luncheon (Box 202, Folder 390)
      - Programs (Box 203, Folder 391)
      - Samples of printed matter (Box 203, Folder 392)
      - Special letters (Box 203, Folder 393)
      - Student Marshalls (Box 203, Folder 394)
    - 1966
      - Correspondence, memoranda (Box 203, Folder 395-397)
      - Luncheon (Box 203, Folder 398)
      - Miscellaneous: seating plans, honorary degree list, programs (Box 203, Folder 399)
      - Programs (Box 203, Folder 400)
      - Requisitions, orders (Box 203, Folder 401)
      - Samples, printed material (Box 204, Folder 402)
      - Student Marshalls (Box 204, Folder 403)
    - 1967
      - Art & Architecture, School of (Box 204, Folder 404)
      - Correspondence, memoranda (Box 204, Folder 405-406)
      - Degrees (Box 204, Folder 407-411)
      - Divinity School (Box 204, Folder 412)
      - Dorr, Harry B. (Box 204, Folder 413)
      - Drama School (Box 204, Folder 414)
      - Engineering, Forestry: School of (Box 204, Folder 415)
      - Graduate School (Box 204, Folder 416)
      - Honorary degrees (Box 204, Folder 417-418)
      - Law School (Box 204, Folder 419)
      - Medicine, School of (Box 204, Folder 420)
      - Military (Box 204, Folder 421)
      - Music School, Nursing School (Box 204, Folder 422)
      - Procedure (Box 204, Folder 423)
      - Procession, programs (Box 205, Folder 424)
      - Programs (Box 205, Folder 425)
      - Requisitions (Box 205, Folder 426)
      - University Council> (Box 205, Folder 427)
    - 1968
      - Calendar, memoranda (Box 205, Folder 428)
      - Correspondence, memoranda (Box 205, Folder 429)
      - Correspondence, memoranda (Box 206, Folder 430)
      - Class Day (Box 206, Folder 431)
      - Programs (Box 206, Folder 432)
    - 1969
      - Class Day (Box 206, Folder 433)
      - Correspondence, memoranda (Box 206, Folder 434)
      - Miscellaneous, correspondence, procedure, programs (Box 206, Folder 435)
      - Procedure, memoranda (Box 206, Folder 436)
      - Programs (Box 206, Folder 437)
  - Crank file, 1953-1966 (Box 207, Folder 438-444)
  - Crank file, 1967 (Box 208, Folder 445-448)
  - Cross, Wilbur, Medal, 1966-1971 (Box 208, Folder 448-A)
  - Degrees: correspondence, 1966-1968 (Box 209, Folder 449)
  - Duplicate diplomas, 1965-1967 (Box 209, Folder 450-452)
  - Henry Fellowships
    - 1948-1952 (Box 209, Folder 453-455)
    - 1956-1957 (Box 210, Folder 456-459)
    - 1956-1966 (Box 210, Folder 460-466)
    - 1957-1959 (Box 211, Folder 467-472)
    - information for directory, 1959 (Box 212, Folder 473-476)
    - questionnaires: Harvard, 1959 (Box 212, Folder 477)
  - Honorary Degrees
    - A-W, 1953-1954 (Box 213, Folder 478-481)
    - A-H, 1955 (Box 213, Folder 482-483)
    - I-W, 1955 (Box 214, Folder 484-485)
    - A-R, 1956 (Box 214, Folder 486-490)
    - S-W, 1956 (Box 215, Folder 491)
    - Miscellaneous, 1956 (Box 215, Folder 492)
    - A-W, 1957 (Box 215, Folder 493-495)
    - Miscellaneous, 1957 (Box 215, Folder 496)
    - A-E, 1958 (Box 215, Folder 497)
    - F-W, 1958 (Box 216, Folder 498-499)
    - Miscellaneous, 1958 (Box 216, Folder 500-501)
    - A-W, 1959 (Box 216, Folder 502-503)
    - Miscellaneous, 1959 (Box 216, Folder 504-505)
    - A-W, 1960 (Box 217, Folder 506-508)
    - Miscellaneous, 1960 (Box 217, Folder 509-511)
    - A-D, 1961 (Box 217, Folder 512)
    - E-N, 1961 (Box 217, Folder 513)
    - O-W, 1961 (Box 218, Folder 514)
    - Miscellaneous, 1961 (Box 218, Folder 515)
    - A-W, 1962 (Box 218, Folder 516-517)
    - Miscellaneous, 1962 (Box 218, Folder 518-520)
    - A-W, 1963 (Box 219, Folder 521-523)
    - Miscellaneous, 1963 (Box 219, Folder 524-526)
    - A-W, 1964 (Box 220, Folder 527-529)
    - Correspondence, 1964 (Box 220, Folder 530-531)
    - Miscellaneous, 1964 (Box 220, Folder 532)
    - A-L, 1965 (Box 220, Folder 533)
    - M-W, 1965 (Box 221, Folder 534)
    - Correspondence, 1965 (Box 221, Folder 535-536)
    - Miscellaneous, 1965 (Box 221, Folder 537-538)
    - A-M, 1966 (Box 221, Folder 539-540)
    - N-Y, 1966 (Box 222, Folder 541-542)
    - Correspondence, 1966 (Box 222, Folder 543)
    - Miscellaneous, 1966 (Box 222, Folder 544)
    - A-W, 1967 (Box 222, Folder 545-546)
    - Awards: past, 1967 (Box 222, Folder 547)
    - Correspondence, 1967 (Box 223, Folder 548)
    - Miscellaneous, 1967 (Box 223, Folder 549-550)
    - A-Y, 1968 (Box 223, Folder 551-555)
    - Miscellaneous, 1968-1971 (Box 223A, Folder 556-559)
  - Inaugurations
    - Griswold, Alfred W., 1950 (Box 224, Folder 560-565)
    - Brewster, Kingman, Jr., 1964 (Box 224, Folder 566-569)
    - Brewster, Kingman, Jr., 1964 (Box 225, Folder 570-577)
    - Brewster, Kingman, Jr., 1964 (Box 226, Folder 578-587)
  - Inaugurations (old): Convocations, Dedications, 1899-1953 (Box 227, Folder 591-597)
  - Invitations for Yale Representation
    - A-Z, 1953-1954 (Box 228, Folder 598-601)
    - A-R, 1954-1955 (Box 228, Folder 602-604)
    - S-Z, 1954-1955 (Box 229, Folder 605)
    - A-Z, 1955-1956 (Box 229, Folder 606-609)
    - A-Z, 1957-1958 (Box 230, Folder 610-613)
    - A-G, 1957-1958 (Box 230, Folder 614-615)
    - H-Z, 1957-1958 (Box 230A, Folder 616-619)
    - A-C, 1958-1959 (Box 230A, Folder 620-621)
    - D-R, 1958-1959 (Box 231, Folder 622-625)
    - S-Z, 1958-1959 (Box 232, Folder 626-627)
    - A-G, 1956-1960 (Box 232, Folder 628-629)
    - H-M, 1956-1960 (Box 233, Folder 630-632)
    - N-Z, 1959-1960 (Box 233, Folder 633-634)
    - N-Z, 1959-1960 (Box 234, Folder 635-638)
    - A-M, 1960-1961 (Box 234, Folder 639)
    - A-M, 1960-1961 (Box 235, Folder 640-644)
    - N-Z, 1960-1961 (Box 236, Folder 645-647)
    - A-M, 1961-1962 (Box 237, Folder 648-652)
    - N-Z, 1961-1962 (Box 238, Folder 653-656)
    - A-Z, 1962-1963 (Box 239, Folder 657-661)
    - Miscellaneous, 1962-1963 (Box 239, Folder 662)
    - A-Z, 1963-1964 (Box 240, Folder 663-667)
    - Miscellaneous, 1963-1964 (Box 240, Folder 668)
    - A-N, 1964-1965 (Box 241, Folder 669-672)
    - O-Z, 1964-1966 (Box 242, Folder 673-674)
    - A-R, 1965-1966 (Box 243, Folder 675-678)
    - S-Z, 1965-1966 (Box 244, Folder 679-680)
    - A-N, 1966-1967 (Box 245, Folder 681-688)
    - N-Z, 1966-1967 (Box 246, Folder 689-693)
    - N-Z, 1966-1967 (Box 247, Folder 694-695)
  - Japan and Yale, 1965 (Box 248, Folder 696)
  - Japan and Yale, 1967-1968 (Box 248, Folder 697)
  - Lectures
    - General, 1952-1966 (Box 249, Folder 698-706)
    - Bergen, 1953-1963 (Box 250, Folder 707-712)
    - Bromley, 1955-1965 (Box 250, Folder 713)
    - Chubb Fellowship, 1954-1965 (Box 250, Folder 714-715)
    - Embree, 1951-1956 (Box 250, Folder 716)
    - Gooch, 1955-1965 (Box 250, Folder 717)
    - Harvard, 1958-1965 (Box 250, Folder 718-719)
    - Hendrickson, 1960-1963 (Box 250, Folder 720)
    - Hoyt Fellow, 1955-1965 (Box 250, Folder 721)
    - Hume, Edward H., 1957-1965 (Box 251, Folder 722-723)
    - Lamont, 1954-1965 (Box 251, Folder 724)
    - Lectureships and visitors, 1952-1961 (Box 251, Folder 725-730)
    - Political Science Conference, 1955 (Box 251, Folder 731)
    - Ray, Isaac, 1953 (Box 252, Folder 732)
    - Records, 1957-1963 (Box 253, Folder 733)
    - Silliman, 1929-1966 (Box 253, Folder 734-747)
    - Terry, 1953-1966 (Box 253, Folder 748-755)
    - Thomas, Ralph Hill, 1956-1965 (Box 253, Folder 756)
    - Trends in science, 1955-1961 (Box 253, Folder 757)
    - Trumbull, 1953-1966 (Box 254, Folder 758-767)
    - University, 1965-1966 (Box 254, Folder 768-772)
    - Woodward, 1953-1966 (Box 255, Folder 773-778, Box 256, Folder 779-784)
  - Library bookplates, undated (Box 257, Folder 785-789)
  - May Day Week-End, 1970
    - Correspondence (Box 258, Folder 790-795)
    - Broadsides (Box 258, Folder 796-797)
    - Burns: fair trial for a black man (Box 258, Folder 798)
    - Faculty alumni support (Box 259, Folder 799)
    - Film project (Box 259, Folder 800-801)
    - Information packet (Box 259, Folder 802)
    - Law School memoranda (Box 259, Folder 803-804)
    - Letters to the Corporation (Box 259, Folder 805)
    - Miscellaneous documents (Box 259, Folder 806)
    - Miscellaneous newspaper duplicates (Box 259, Folder 807)
    - Operation watchdog (Box 259, Folder 808)
    - Outside press (Box 260, Folder 809-811)
    - President Brewster's statements (Box 260, Folder 812)
    - Strike: newspaper duplicates (Box 260, Folder 813)
    - University Preparations and Plans (Box 260, Folder 814)
    - Yale Daily News duplicates (Box 260, Folder 815)
    - Yale publications (Box 261, Folder 816-818)
  - Prizes, Scholarships [extinct]
    - Administrative Science, 1971 (Box 262, Folder 819)
    - Art and Architecture, School of, 1953-1958 (Box 262, Folder 820)
    - Barnes, John Hampton, 1957 (Box 262, Folder 821)
    - Carnegie-Yale, 1958 (Box 262, Folder 822)
    - Dante, 1955 (Box 262, Folder 826)
    - Engineering School, 1954-1966 (Box 262, Folder 827)
    - German, 1957-1963 (Box 262, Folder 828-831)
    - Green, C.W. Douglass, 1966-1968 (Box 263, Folder 832-833)
    - Letters on prizes, 1969 (Box 263, Folder 834)
    - Metcalf, 1965 (Box 263, Folder 835)
    - Miscellaneous material, 1950-1966 (Box 263, Folder 836)
    - Mitchell, Sidney Knox, 1961-1966 (Box 263, Folder 837)
    - New York Yale Club, 1952-1966 (Box 263, Folder 838)
    - Overbrook, 1960-1968 (Box 263, Folder 839)
    - Plimpton, Chester Harding, 1953-1966 (Box 263, Folder 840)
    - Scherrill, Henry Knox, 1960-1968 (Box 263, Folder 842)
    - Von Humboldt, Alexander, 1960-1962 (Box 263, Folder 843)
    - Webb, Gertie Emily Gorman, 1952 (Box 263, Folder 844)
    - Yale-Heidelberg, 1952-1959 (Box 263, Folder 845-846)
  - Reserve Officer Training Corps [ROTC]
    - Advisory panel, 1969-1971 (Box 264, Folder 847-853)
    - Advisory panel, 1969-1971 (Box 265, Folder 854-855)
    - American Universities Survey, The Association of, 1970 (Box 265, Folder 856)
    - Army, 1968-1970 (Box 265, Folder 857-861)
    - Army and Navy, 1970-1971 (Box 266, Folder 862)
    - Brewster, President: special report of alumni, 1969 (Box 266, Folder 863)
    - Meetings, 1966-1969 (Box 266, Folder 864-867)
    - Miscellaneous, 1969 (Box 267, Folder 868-871)
    - National Guard Plan, undated (Box 268, Folder 872)
    - Naval Science, Department of, 1968-1969 (Box 268, Folder 873)
    - Navy, 1969-1970 (Box 268, Folder 874)
    - Navy agreement, 1969 (Box 268, Folder 875)
    - New Senior Program, 1969 (Box 268, Folder 876)
    - Officer Education Study Vol. II, 1966 (Box 268, Folder 877-878)
    - Pamphlets, clippings, 1969 (Box 269, Folder 879)
    - World War II training, 1941-1942 (Box 269, Folder 880)
  - Russian Exchange
    - Correspondence, 1959-1963 (Box 269, Folder 881-882)
    - Heidelberg affiliation, 1953-1955 (Box 269, Folder 883)
    - Newspaper clippings on Russian education, 1957-1961 (Box 269, Folder 884-885)
    - Post-doctoral studies and correspondence, 1959-1963 (Box 269, Folder 886)
  - Senior Class Day, 1959-1970 (Box 270, Folder 887-895)
  - Services of remembrance, 1950-1967 (Box 270, Folder 896-897)
  - Special Events
    - Angell: 100th birthday, 1969 (Box 272, Folder 903)
    - Barghoorn incident, 1963 (Box 272, Folder 904)
    - Becton Center: dedication, 1970 (Box 272, Folder 905)
    - Becton cornerstone, 1968 (Box 272, Folder 906)
    - Becton Laboratory, 1969-1970 (Box 272, Folder 907)
    - Blair, Edwin Foster dinner, 1970 (Box 272, Folder 908)
    - Breit symposium, 1968 (Box 272, Folder 909)
    - Brewster, Kingman, Jr.: election as president, 1963 (Box 272, Folder 910)
    - Brewster, Kingman, Jr.: fifth anniversary, 1968 (Box 272, Folder 911)
    - Carillon dedication, 1966 (Box 272, Folder 912)
    - Chase, Betsy reception, 1970 (Box 272, Folder 913)
    - Dante's birth: 700th anniversary, 1965-1966 (Box 273, Folder 914)
    - DeVane bust unveiling, 1968 (Box 273, Folder 915)
    - DeVane memorial service, 1965 (Box 273, Folder 916)
    - Devane: Phi Beta Kappa banquet in honor of, 1966 (Box 273, Folder 917)
    - Drama School 40th anniversary, 1965-1966 (Box 273, Folder 918)
    - Eisenhower memorial service, 1969 (Box 273, Folder 919)
    - Ezra Stiles and Morse College dedication, 1962 (Box 273, Folder 920-921)
    - Fisher, Irving Centennial, 1967 (Box 274, Folder 922)
    - Golf course: watering system, 1968 (Box 274, Folder 923)
    - Graduate and professional schools assembly, 1953-1954 (Box 274, Folder 924)
    - Griswold, A. Whitney, 1963 (Box 274, Folder 925)
    - Griswold plaque, 1968 (Box 274, Folder 926)
    - Harvard ceremony for President Pusey, 1954 (Box 274, Folder 927-928)
    - Harvard weekend thank-you letters, 1954 (Box 274, Folder 929)
    - Hunter Radiation Center: addition, 1965-1966 (Box 274, Folder 930)
    - King, Martin Luther death, 1968 (Box 274, Folder 931)
    - Kiphuth memorial, 1968 (Box 274, Folder 932)
    - Kline Biology Tower: dedication, 1966 (Box 274, Folder 933)
    - Laboratory of Clinical Investigation: dedication, 1965 (Box 275, Folder 934)
    - Medical Library plaque unveiling, 1969 (Box 275, Folder 935)
    - Memorial service for eight students, 1962 (Box 275, Folder 936)
    - Mental Health, Connecticut, dedication, 1966 (Box 275, Folder 937)
    - Morse and Ezra Stiles: new residential colleges, 1962-1963 (Box 275, Folder 938)
    - Music Centennial, 1954-1955 (Box 275, Folder 939)
    - Music School: 75th anniversary, 1969-1970 (Box 275, Folder 940)
    - National Historic Landmarks, 1967 (Box 275, Folder 941)
    - New Haven Symphony: 75th anniversary, 1969 (Box 275, Folder 942)
    - Nuclear Structure Laboratory dedication, 1966 (Box 275, Folder 943)
    - Obookiah ceremony, 1968 (Box 275, Folder 944)
    - Ore, Oystein Symposium, 1968 (Box 275, Folder 945)
    - Peabody Museum Centennial, 1966 (Box 276, Folder 946-947)
    - Pediatric facility on Hunter 4 dedication, 1966 (Box 276, Folder 948)
    - Pharmacology dedication, 1967 (Box 276, Folder 949)
    - Phelps Hall, 1967 (Box 276, Folder 950)
    - Phi Beta Kappa dinner, 1968 (Box 276, Folder 951)
    - Sizer memorial service, 1967 (Box 276, Folder 952)
    - Stagg, A.A.: 100th birthday, 1962 (Box 276, Folder 953)
    - Students for a Democratic Society, 1969 (Box 276, Folder 954)
    - Trumbull Stamp ceremony, 1968 (Box 277, Folder 955)
    - Wallace incident, 1963 (Box 277, Folder 956)
    - Webster, Noah: 200th anniversary, 1958 (Box 277, Folder 957)
    - Wetlands Committee Inc., 1968-1969 (Box 277, Folder 958)
    - Wittstein, Eddie: presentation, 1967 (Box 277, Folder 959)
    - Yale Daily News: memorial edition of the, 1965 (Box 277, Folder 960)
    - Yale in New Haven: 250th anniversary, 1966 (Box 277, Folder 961)
    - Yale Shakespeare Festival, 1954 (Box 277, Folder 962)
  - Special Reports
    - Alumni Affairs: Study of the report of the commission, 1971 (Box 278, Folder 963)
    - Audio-Visual Center: memoranda, undated (Box 278, Folder 964)
    - Bachelor of Arts: Annual report on the experimental five-year program, 1969-1970 (Box 278, Folder 965)
    - Capital funds for university's libraries, 1964 (Box 278, Folder 966)
    - Class of 1965: profile of (Box 278, Folder 967)
    - Committee on Discipline Report of the President's, 1968 (Box 278, Folder 968)
    - "Computers for the Humanities?,", 1965 (Box 278, Folder 969)
    - Council, Yale University (Box 278, Folder 970)
    - Development Board Convocation: Yale transcript, 1970 (Box 278, Folder 971)
    - Drug Dependent Institute for Training and Research, 1970-1971 (Box 278, Folder 972)
    - Educational planning, [1970-1971?] (Box 278, Folder 973)
    - Employment Program Committee: undergraduate, 1971 (Box 278, Folder 974)
    - Engineering education at Yale University, 1961 (Box 278, Folder 975)
    - Film Committee, 1965 (Box 278, Folder 976)
    - Foreign Student Institute, 1964 (Box 279, Folder 978)
    - Foreign students and post doctoral fellows, 1970-1971 (Box 279, Folder 979)
    - Fulbright Scholars, a report on the conference of, 1962 (Box 279, Folder 980)
    - Hall Report, The, 1968 (Box 279, Folder 981)
    - International studies, ten year plan, 1960 (Box 279, Folder 982)
    - Junior Faculty research support proposal, 1962 (Box 279, Folder 983)
    - Junior Science and Humanities Symposium, 1967 (Box 279, Folder 984)
    - Needs of Yale, The Ten year, 1966-1967, 1967 (Box 279, Folder 985)
    - Nursing Education, Yale and, undated (Box 279, Folder 986)
    - Obligations for Yale University, A Bill of, 1968 (Box 279, Folder 987)
    - Ophthomology: Report of Activity, 1968-1970 (Box 279, Folder 988)
    - Peace Corps: Senior Year Training Program, 1964 (Box 279, Folder 989)
    - President's Special Committee, Summary of Recommendations by, 1959 (Box 280, Folder 990)
    - Sex descrimination at Yale, 1971 (Box 280, Folder 991)
    - Simpson Report on University Administration, 1958 (Box 280, Folder 992)
    - Social Science, Institute of, 1970 (Box 280, Folder 993)
    - Social Studies, Twelfth Yale Conference on the Teachings of, 1967 (Box 280, Folder 994)
    - Steering Committee Report to Faculty, 1965 (Box 280, Folder 995)
    - Sterling Library: Selective Book Retirement Program, undated (Box 280, Folder 996)
    - Study of 221 students who dropped out of college and returned, 1961-1964 (Box 280, Folder 997)
    - Summer High School: Yale, 1965 (Box 280, Folder 998)
    - Urban Studies Program, 1967 (Box 280, Folder 999)
    - Volunteer Services, Office of, 1970-1971 (Box 280, Folder 1000)
    - Women at Yale, Status of, 1971 (Box 280, Folder 1001)
    - Yale and the Schools, undated (Box 280, Folder 1002)
  - Student Activities, 1969
    - Brewster, Kingman, Jr.: statements (Box 281, Folder 1003)
    - Campus fliers (Box 281, Folder 1004)
    - Coalition for a new university (Box 281, Folder 1005)
    - Disturbances (Box 281, Folder 1006)
    - Press coverage (Box 281, Folder 1007)
    - Protests (Box 281, Folder 1008)
    - Statements (Box 281, Folder 1009)
    - Student activism (Box 281, Folder 1010)
    - University general meetings (Box 281, Folder 1011)
  - "Town and Gown"
    - Community based projects, 1960-1968 (Box 282, Folder 1012-1014)
    - Meetings, 1959-1962 (Box 282, Folder 1015-1016)
    - Police Science and Administration Program, undated (Box 282, Folder 1017)
    - "Yale Your Neighbor": Radio Station WELI, 1961 (Box 282, Folder 1018)
    - Youth Welfare, Committee on, 1959-1960 (Box 282, Folder 1019)
  - University Council Correspondence
    - Advisory Council, 1947 (Box 283, Folder 1020)
    - Affairs, University Committee on, 1947-1948 (Box 283, Folder 1021)
    - Aldrich, Malcolm P., 1957-1958 (Box 283, Folder 1022)
    - Altschul, Frank, 1955-1959 (Box 283, Folder 1023)
    - Alumni Organizations: Committee on, 1948-1954 (Box 283, Folder 1024)
    - Ashburn, Frank, 1951-1954 (Box 283, Folder 1025)
    - Brochure, 1947 (Box 283, Folder 1026)
    - Commbe, Reginald G., 1953-1955 (Box 283, Folder 1027)
    - Cooper, James W., 1958-1959 (Box 283, Folder 1028)
    - Data and suggestions, 1948-1950 (Box 283, Folder 1029-1030)
    - Development, 1946-1951 (Box 284, Folder 1031-1033)
    - Early, 1947-1948 (Box 284, Folder 1034)
    - Executive Committee, 1947-1951 (Box 284, Folder 1035-1036)
    - Forestry School, Committee on, 1947-1955 (Box 284, Folder 1037-1039)
    - Given, William B., Jr., 1947-1948 (Box 285, Folder 1040)
    - Humanities, Committee on the, 1947-1952 (Box 285, Folder 1041)
    - Invitations, Listening Posts, 1948-1950 (Box 285, Folder 1042-1043)
    - Members at large, 1948-1950 (Box 285, Folder 1044)
    - Medical Affairs, Committee on, 1948-1953 (Box 285, Folder 1045-1046)
    - Military and Naval Affairs, Committee on (Box 286, Folder 1047)
    - Miscellaneous, 1959-1961 (Box 286, Folder 1048-1050)
    - Olds, Irving S., 1959-1960 (Box 286, Folder 1051)
    - Pictures, undated (Box 286, Folder 1052)
    - Planning and Developing, 1940-1948 (Box 286, Folder 1053)
    - Publicity, 1948 (Box 286, Folder 1054)
    - Religious Life and Study, 1948-1955 (Box 287, Folder 1055-1056)
    - Robinson, Jucius F., Jr., 1959-1961 (Box 287, Folder 1057)
    - Sciences, Committee on, 1947-1957 (Box 287, Folder 1058-1059)
    - Social Studies, Committee on, 1949-1957 (Box 287, Folder 1060-1061)
    - Suggestions for the presidency, 1947-1950 (Box 287, Folder 1062)
    - "Yale News" editorial, 1948 (Box 287, Folder 1063)
  - University Council Meetings
    - First, 1948 February 22 (Box 288, Folder 1064)
    - Second, 1948 May 15 (Box 288, Folder 1065)
    - Third, 1949 November 20 (Box 288, Folder 1066)
    - Fourth, 1949 May 6-7 (Box 288, Folder 1067)
    - Fifth, 1949 October 28 (Box 288, Folder 1068)
    - Sixth, 1950 May 5 (Box 288, Folder 1069)
    - Seventh, 1950 November 3 (Box 288, Folder 1070)
    - Eighth, 1951 May 4 (Box 288, Folder 1071)
    - Ninth, 1951 November 2 (Box 288, Folder 1072)
    - Tenth, 1952 May 16 (Box 288, Folder 1073)
    - Eleventh, 1952 December 5 (Box 288, Folder 1074)
    - Twelfth, 1953 May 15 (Box 288, Folder 1075)
    - Thirteenth, 1953 November 20 (Box 288, Folder 1076)
    - Fourteenth, 1954 May 14 (Box 288, Folder 1077)
    - Fifteenth, 1954 December 3 (Box 288, Folder 1078)
  - University Council Reports, 1951-1952 (Box 289, Folder 1079-1983)
  - University Council Reports, 1952-1953 (Box 290, Folder 1084-1987)
  - Ushers, 1956-1964 (Box 291, Folder 1088-1096)
  - Visitors
    - 1951-1952 (Box 292, Folder 1097)
    - A-Z, 1953-1955 (Box 292, Folder 1098-1104)
    - A-C, 1955-1956 (Box 292, Folder 1105)
    - D-Z, 1955-1956 (Box 293, Folder 1106-1108)
    - The nine Russian priests, 1956 (Box 293, Folder 1109)
    - A-Z, 1956-1957 (Box 293, Folder 1110-1113)
    - A-Z, 1957-1958 (Box 294, Folder 1114-1118)
    - A-B, 1958-1959 (Box 294, Folder 1119)
    - Association of Universities of The British Commonwealth, 1958 (Box 294, Folder 1120)
    - Business cards, 1958-1959 (Box 294, Folder 1121)
    - C, 1958-1959 (Box 294, Folder 1122)
    - D-Z, 1958-1959 (Box 295, Folder 1123-1131)
    - A-Z, 1959-1960 (Box 296, Folder 1132-1138)
    - A-Ha, 1960-1961 (Box 297, Folder 1139-1146)
    - Hi-Z, 1960-1961 (Box 298, Folder 1147-1154)
    - A-P, 1961-1962 (Box 299, Folder 1155-1162)
    - Q-Z, 1961-1962 (Box 300, Folder 1163-1164)
    - A-P, 1962-1963 (Box 300, Folder 1165-1170)
    - P-Z, 1962-1963 (Box 301, Folder 1171-1174)
  - Weekly Calendar, 1970 September-1971 May (Box 302, Folder 1175-1183)
  - World War II: letters of approval from families for memorial tablets, 1947-1948 (Box 303, Folder 1184-1191)
  - Yale, Elihu, 1874-1966 (Box 304, Folder 1192-1194)
  - Yale, Elihu: genealogy, 1843 (Box 304, Folder 1195)
  - Yale, Elihu: Royal and Noble heritage of, undated (Box 304, Folder 1196-1197)
  - Yale, Elihu and Madras, India, 1961-1968 (Box 304, Folder 1198-1199)